[{"answer": "It's actually a subpoena.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Is it a lawsuit?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Just like this -- never.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "When was it?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, you invited me and I'm intrigued by you, and I'm someone who watches your show almost every night, and I'm just intrigued and also, of course, it's an opportunity to talk about empowering women, empowering minorities and the fact that we still have not won complete equality in this country.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Why are you doing this?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, I'm the Gloria Allred who is an attorney at part of our law firm of Allred, Marco and Goldberg.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Which Gloria Allred are you?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I do believe that, under the law, under the Constitution of the United States, and under our public policy, that women deserve and should have a right to enjoy equal employment opportunity.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Do you believe that men and women should be absolutely equal in everything?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "We do cases of public interest and importance.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Do you ever do anything for publicity?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "It really depends on the particular facts.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Or should there be equality because simply because a woman may not have the power of a man to play to that ability?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, we have --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you feel as aggrieved for men who get treated badly by women bosses?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, we actually have had a number of cases, where we represent men who have been discriminated against in employment, on account of their gender.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Or is it all women against men?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "No, not at all, because we are a plaintiff's law firm.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Does that worry you?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, I like empowering my clients.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Do you like that status?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, it matters if any man hurts any woman.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Why did you feel compelled to expose him?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "They had -- she had -- she was an adult film star, yes.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "She was a porn, right?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And I just wonder sometimes, when you watch what she did afterwards, do you slightly sit back and go, maybe I should have left that one alone?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "No, I'm so proud of my clients and the courage they've shown.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Do you ever regret afterwards taking on cases, because of the way that perhaps the person you've been defending or prosecuting on behalf of, because of their behavior afterwards, you have moments of self-reflection afterwards?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Of course, she did.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Does she -- does she not care about Ms. Woods?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I get that.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "But do you care about women being hurt by men whom they trusted, whom they loved, who they had every reason to believe loved them?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "They have to survive.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Ever?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, we represent victims' rights.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Or is it always strictly legal?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I think that if --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Should having an affair preclude a man from running for office?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I think that politicians, if they are going to seek the highest office in our land, the presidency of the United States of America, they need to be honest with the American public, and just put it all out there, and not be hypocrites, not present themselves as the perfect family man.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "So, where do you draw the line?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, let me just say -- I mean, I'm not a person who's going to vote for any of the potential Republican nominees for the presidency of the United States.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Are you happy for him to restart politically, if you like?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What happened to that guy that raped you?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I never did.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Did you ever see or hear of him again?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Never found out.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "You never found out what happened to him?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "LLRED: You know, I generally don't look back.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What are your feelings towards him now?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "You know, it wasn't about forgiving.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Were you able to forgive your first husband for the abuse when you discovered about this bipolar?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "She's pretty special, your mother.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "How great is my mom?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "She's given it to you, hasn't she?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I'll answer, too.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Does she?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "And no one can remember when I took a vacation --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I've had a vacation -- well, years ago, I took my grandchildren on vacations --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "You never have a vacation?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Because I have too much to do to fight injustice that still exists for my clients, for women and minorities.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "ORGAN: Why?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "You have a 10-year-old car, is that true?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Can I -- let me respond to that, Piers, because --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "But then -- but then I come back to the Tiger Woods case that you heard us debating earlier where I kind of think, why would this women, who does all this incredible stuff, take on a porn star to basically flim/flam Tiger Woods, really?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what I think.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Most of what she does.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Or the age discrimination case that we won?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Were you as proud?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "May I finish, please?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I'm just wondering whether, when your mother takes on a case like that, which is obviously so high-profile, obviously going to get so much attention, when you see this victim as she's being portrayed, go on to make another movie --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Then why are you saying \"porn star,\" as if that's relevant?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "-- in which she uses Tiger Woods --", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Well, so what?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "And she's a victim.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "And exploit it and commercialize it?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "He did apologize.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "And why don't you spend as much talking about the fact that Tiger Woods should apologize to the women that he hurt?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I love my mother.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Well, do you like having this famous, infamous mother?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Does she get mischaracterized, do you think?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "None.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "How much of that is her own fault for taking on cases which are inflammatory?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Listen, we're talking about the media.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Why does your mother take on celebrity cases?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "Because I don't consider them to be scandalous celebrity cases.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Can you not persuade your mother to drop all the scandalous celebrity cases?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "They're not scandalous celebrity cases.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "LOOM: The media -- because I care about them and they have viable -- they're human beings, Piers.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love, Gloria?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "It's actually a subpoena.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "ORGAN: Is it a lawsuit?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Would you like to fall in love again?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "No, I don't have time, and I don't want to make that investment.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Much younger men.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "We have a saying in the women's movement, become the person you wanted to marry.", "docId": "120323pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 687}]